robinreads.com 2019-02-05

# Privacy Policy and Terms of Service

**Last Updated: May 21st 2018**

RobinReads (“Company”, “we”, or “us”) is committed to protecting your privacy. We have prepared this privacy policy to describe to you our practices regarding the personal information we collect from users of our website, located at https:// RobinReads .com (the “Site”) and online services (“Services”).

**Privacy of Minors**  
Protecting the privacy of children is very important to us. We do not intentionally collect or maintain Personal Information from people we actually know are under 18. If we later learn that a user is under 18, we will take steps to remove that user’s personal information from our databases and to prevent the user from utilizing the Site and the Service.

Robin Reads is serious about maintaining your privacy. We don’t like to get spam, and can appreciate that you don’t want to get any either. So, here’s the deal…  
If you provide us feedback or contact us via email, we will collect your name and email address, as well as any other content included in the email, in order to send you a reply.

**What Information is Collected**  
When you visit Robin Reads my webserver automatically logs the following information, which I use to understand general usage of the website. This is completely standard. Pretty much every single website on the entire Internet stores traffic logs exactly like this.

* Your IP address  
* What pages were visited, and when  
* What site you were on before you came to Robin Reads  
* Your web browser software manufacturer and version (i.e. Mozilla 5.0)  
* Your operating software manufacturer and version (i.e. Windows Vista)

This information is collected completely anonymously. So, We don’t know who you are, just that someone came to the website and looked at a few pages.You can opt out of our email subscription service at any time by clicking the “unsubscribe link” at the bottom of every email.

**Advertising Network**  
robinreads.com uses Google as a third-party vendor to serve advertisements on the website. Google uses the Doubleclick DART cookie to serve ads to you based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  
The owner of this website, is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking Robin Reads to Amazon properties including, but not limited to, amazon.com, endless.com, myhabit.com, smallparts.com, or amazonwireless.com.  
robinreads.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com. Our goal is to provide our readers with a curated list of some of the best free ebooks for Kindle each day. We also provide notifications of bargain ebooks and any ebooks deals we can find.

**How We Use Your Information**  
In general, we use the information we collect to either respond to the requests you make, or to aid us in serving you better. We use your personal information in the following ways: (i) to facilitate the creation of and secure your Account on our network; (ii) identify you as a user in our system; (iii) provide improved administration of our Site and Services; (iv) provide the Services you request; (v) to improve the quality of experience when you interact with our Site and Services; (vi) send you a welcome email; (vii) send you administrative email notifications, such as security or support and maintenance advisories; (viii) respond to your inquiries; and (ix) to send newsletters, surveys, offers and other promotional materials related to our Services and for other marketing purposes of the Company.  
We may also create anonymous data from your personal information by excluding information (such as your name) that makes the data personally identifiable to you. We use this anonymous data to analyze request and usage patterns so that we may enhance the content of our Services and improve Site navigation. 

**How to Opt Out**  
We will periodically send you free newsletters and emails that directly promote the use or our Site or Services. When you receive newsletters or promotional communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further communications from us and you will have the opportunity to “opt-out” by clicking on the link at the bottom of any of your emails and following the unsubscribe instructions provided.  
If you wish to opt out of future promotional communications from us, you may also click our contact us form  
Despite your indicated email preferences, we may send you service related communications, including notices of any updates to our Terms of Service or Privacy Policy.

**THIRD PARTY WEBSITES**  
The Site contains links to third party Web sites. Please be aware that we have no control over, do not review, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other Web sites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site they visit. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by us through the Site.
